Guide to the William Upcott, Original Letters
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
"Original letters collected by William Upcott of the London Institution. Marquesses. Second series."
1824-1824
OSBORN D195
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
0.16
(1 volume)
Autograph MSS. Letters mounted in an album.
Upcott, William, 1779-1845
Immediate Source of Acquisition
For provenance information, consult the appropriate curator.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Scope and Contents
The following finding aid is a complete inventory of the contents of Osborn d195. This list was reformatted from previously existing cataloging.
Autographs -- Great Britain; Nobility -- Great Britain; Upcott, William, 1779-1845
- Osborn d195
  - ABERCORN, ANNE JANE HAMILTON, MARCHIONESS OF, 1763-1827
    - AL (in third person) to Kent and Luck, firm, 1805 Mar 15 (Box 1)
      Scope and Contents
      Green St.
      1 p.; 18 x 12 cm.
      Requests that her carpet be put down.
      d 195/2
  - AILESBURY, CHARLES BRUDENELL-BRUCE, 1ST MARQUIS OF, 1773-1856
    - AL (in third person) to Lackington and Co., booksellers, 1819 Mar 3 (Box 1)
      Grosvenor Square
      1 p.; 23 x 19 cm.
      Wishes to be a subscriber to the
      "History of Antient Wiltshire" by
      Sir Richard Colt Hoare, 2nd bart.
      (1758-1838).
      d 195/4
  - AILESBURY, HENRIETTA MARIA, MARCHIONESS OF, D. 1831
    - AL to Maria Louisa Catherine Cecilia (Hadfield) Cosway (1759-1838), [ca. 1820] (Box 1)
      [London]
      1 p.; 8 x 19 cm.
      Lady Ailesbury will call with her
      niece and husband.
      d 195/5
  - ANTRIM, CHARLOTTE (MCDONNELL) KERR, COUNTESS OF, 1779-1835
    - AL (in third person) to Roberts and Plowman, firm, [no yr.] May 5 (Box 1)
      n.p.
      2 p.; 19 x 12 cm.
      Asks for patterns of fabrics.
      d 195/81
  - BATH, ISABELLA ELIZABETH THYNNE, MARCHIONESS OF, 1773-1830
    - AL (in third person) to Mr. Rodwell, bookseller, 1818 Mar 30 (Box 1)
      Lower Green Street
      1 p.; 18 x 11 cm.
      Order for publications.
      d 195/13
  - BATH, ISABELLA ELIZABETH THYNNE, MARCHIONESS OF, 1773-1830
    - AL (in third person) to Mr. King, bookseller, [1816] (Box 1)
      [1816 or later (paper WM 1816)]
      Orders books.
      d 195/14
  - BATH, THOMAS THYNNE, 2ND MARQUIS OF, 1765-1837
    - ALS to Conrad Loddiges (1732-1826), 1811 Dec 18 (Box 1)
      Longleat
      Requests plants; a draft of a reply
      by Loddiges on p. 4 of the letter.
      Gardening.
      d.195/12
  - BERESFORD, LADY CATHERINE
    - AL (in third person) to Conrad Loddiges (1732-1826), 1814 Jan 14 (Box 1)
      20 Upper Harley Street
      1 p.; 23 x 18 cm.
      Orders flower seeds.
      d.195/106
  - BERESFORD, JOHN CLAUDIUS, 1766-1846
    - ALS to Thomas Bainbridge of Paget Bainbridge and Co., bankers, 1810 Aug 9 (Box 1)
      Waterford
      1 p.; 25 x 20 cm.
      Concerns a banking transaction.
      d.195/107
  - BUTE, CHARLOTTE JANE STUART, MARCHIONESS OF, 1746-1801
    - AL (in third person) to Conrad Loddiges (1732-1826), 1798 Apr 24 (Box 1)
      Hill Street
      2 p.; 23 x 18 cm.
      Requests that he put identification
      tickets or sticks on each pot he
      sends her.
      d.195/19
  - BUTE, JOHN CRICHTON-STUART, 2ND MARQUIS OF, 1793-1848
    - ALS to an unnamed recipient, 1818 Oct 20 (Box 1)
      Reply to an invitation.
      d.195/18xx
  - BUTE, JOHN STUART, 1ST MARQUIS OF, 1744-1814
    - ALS to an unnamed recipient, [no year] Aug 8 (Box 1)
      Portland Street
      1 p.; 22 x 18 cm.
      Asks advice concerning the purchase
      of Napoleons.
      d.195/18
  - BUTE, JOHN STUART, 1ST MARQUIS OF, 1744-1814
    - ALS to Mr. Greenwood, auctioneer of Bond St., 1807 Jun 12 (Box 1)
      Luton Park
      Thanks him for sending an assistant
      to arrange books and seeks a picture
      to match his Velazquez.
      d.195/18x
  - BUTE, MARY (WORTLEY MONTAGU) STUART, COUNTESS OF, 1718-1794
    - ALS to an unnamed recipient, 1782 Nov 5 (Box 1)
      London
      Concerns money to be paid by
      occupants of some land.
      d.195/20
  - BUTLER, DOROTHEA, LADY BUTLER
    - ALS to Paget Bainbridge and Co., bankers, 1804 Sep 19 (Box 1)
      Weymouth
      1 p.; 24 x 18 cm.
      Requests that £60 be sent.
      d.195/91
  - BUTLER, J. H.
    - ALS to Paget Bainbridge & Co., bankers, 1803 Feb 15 (Box 1)
      Calne
      Concerns the finances of Lady
      Ormonde.
      d.195/88
  - BUTLER, J. H.
    - ALS to Paget Bainbridge & Co., bankers, 1804 Sep 28 (Box 1)
      Brabburn Lees
      Thanks for an offer which he
      declines.
      d.195/89
  - BUTLER, LOUISA, LADY BUTLER
    - AL (in third person) to Paget Bainbridge and Co., bankers, 1808 Nov 1 (Box 1)
      Twickenham
      Requests £90 Irish.
      d.195/90
  - CAMDEN, GEORGE CHARLES PRATT, 2ND MARQUIS OF, 1799-1866
    - ALS to an unnamed recipient, [no yr.] May 25 (Box 1)
      Arlington Street
      1 p.; 24 x 19 cm.
      Requests that the "picture of Lord
      Brecknock" [John Jeffreys Pratt, 1st
      Marquis of Camden, 1759-1840] be
      sent.
      d.195/25
  - CAMDEN, JOHN JEFFREYS PRATT, 1ST MARQUIS OF, 1759-1840
    - AL (in third person) to Mr. Leigh, [no yr.] Aug 17 (Box 1)
      Cowes
      Orders Gagliani's books [?Ferdinando
      Galiani (1728-1787)] on Italy and
      France.
      d.195/26
  - CAMDEN, JOHN JEFFREYS PRATT, 1ST MARQUIS OF, 1759-1840
    - AL (in third person) to the Lord Mayor of London, 1827 Oct 22 (Box 1)
      Wilderness Park
      2 p.; 18 x 12 cm.
      Presents his regrets to an
      invitation.
      d.195/26x
  - CHOMONDELEY, GEORGE JAMES CHOLMONDELEY, MARQUIS OF, 1749-1827
    - AL (in third person) to the London Auxiliary Bible Society, 1820 Oct 17 (Box 1)
      He cannot attend the meetings but he
      encloses his subscription.
      d.195/29
  - CHOMONDELEY, GEORGE JAMES CHOLMONDELEY, MARQUIS OF, 1749-1827
    - ALS to the London Auxiliary Bible Society, 1821 Oct 25 (Box 1)
      Cholmondeley House
      He will attend the meeting.
      d.195/30
  - CHOMONDELEY, GEORGE JAMES CHOLMONDELEY, MARQUIS OF, 1749-1827
    - 2 ALS to the Lord Mayor Elect [of London], 1820-24 (Box 1)
      1820 Nov 2 and 1824 Nov 7
      2 p.; 24 x 18 cm.
      Declines invitations to the
      Guildhall dinners.
      d.195/27,28
  - CHOLMONDELEY, HON. MRS.
    - AL (incomplete) to an unnamed recipient, [ca. 1800] (Box 1)
      Jan 24, [Petersham]
      4 p.; 30 x 19 cm.
      Fragment of a letter written
      apparently near to her death; she
      discusses her personal health and
      her present situation; the tone of
      the letter is one of desperation.
      d.195/30x
  - COMPTON, MARGARET (CLEOPHANE), LADY COMPTON, D. 1830
    - 2 ALS to Lackington and Co., booksellers, 1818 Jul, 13 (Box 1)
      Saville Row
      4 p.; 16 x 10 cm.
      On the purchase of books.
      d.195/81xx,81xxx
  - CONYNGHAM, ELIZABETH CONYNGHAM, MARCHIONESS, 1769-1861
    - 2 AL (in third person) to Kent and Luck, firm (Box 1)
      Hamilton Place
      2 p.; 22 x 18 cm.
      Carpets on order.
      d.195/33,34
  - CONYNGHAM, HENRY CONYNGHAM, 1ST MARQUIS, 1766-1832
    - AL (in third person) to Kent and Luck, firm. (Box 1)
      Stanhope Street
      Requests that a carpet be sent.
      d.195/32
  - CONYNGHAM, HENRY CONYNGHAM, 1ST MARQUIS, 1766-1832
    - AL (in third person) to the Lord Mayor Elect and Sheriffs [of London], 1826 Oct 24 (Box 1)
      [R.?] Lodge
      2 p.; 18 x 11 cm.
      Declines an invitation to dine.
      d.195/32x
  - CONYNGHAM, HENRY CONYNGHAM, 1ST MARQUIS, 1766-1832
    - AL to the Lord Mayor Elect and Sheriffs [of London], [1822] (Box 1)
      1 p.; 8 x 11 cm.
      Accepts invitation to dinner.
      d.195/34x
  - DOWNSHIRE, ARTHUR BLUNDELL HILL, 3RD MARQUIS OF, 1788-1845
    - AL to the Lord Mayor Elect [of London], 1820 Nov 8 (Box 1)
      House of Lords
      Declines a dinner invitation.
      d.195/35
  - DOWNSHIRE, ARTHUR HILL, 4TH MARQUIS OF, 1812-1868
    - AL to the Lord Mayor Elect [of London], [no yr] Nov 9 (Box 1)
      Hanover Square
      Accepts an invitation.
      d.195/36x
  - DOWNSHIRE, MARIA (WINDSOR) HILL, MARCHIONESS OF, 1790-1855
    - AL to [John Thomas] Smith (1766-1833), n.d. (Box 1)
      1 p.; 11 x 9 cm.
      Extends an invitation to Mr. Smith.
      d.195/36
  - ELY, ANNA MARIA (DASHWOOD) LOFTUS, MARCHIONESS OF, 1785-1857
    - AL to Cadell and Davies, publishers, 1809 Nov 5 (Box 1)
      Windsor Castle
      On behalf of Princess Augusta
      (1768-1840) and Princess Elizabeth,
      princess of England and landgravine
      of Heese-Homburg (1770-1840), she
      requests a copy of the poem
      "Wallace" by Margaret (Holford)
      Hodson (1778-1852).
      d.195/46
  - ELY, JANE (MYHILL) TOTTENHAM, MARCHIONESS OF, D. 1807
    - AL to Paget, Bainbridge and Co., bankers, 1800 Sep 14 (Box 1)
      Clifton
      Receipt for bills received.
      d.195/37
  - ELY, JANE (MYHILL) TOTTENHAM, MARCHIONESS OF, D. 1807
    - ALS to Paget, Bainbridge and Co., bankers, 1806 Jul 14 (Box 1)
      Bath
      Receipt for a draft sent.
      d.195/38
  - ELY, JOHN LOFTUS, 2ND MARQUIS OF, 1770-1845
    - AL to Paget, Bainbridge and Co., bankers, [1806] (Box 1)
      [1806 Mar or earlier]
      Blake's Hotel, Jermyn Street
      Wishes to see his account.
      d.195/39
  - ELY, JOHN LOFTUS, 2ND MARQUIS OF, 1770-1845
    - ALS to Paget, Bainbridge and Co., bankers, 1806 Mar 27 (Box 1)
      Dublin
      d.195/40
  - ELY, JOHN LOFTUS, 2ND MARQUIS OF, 1770-1845
    - ALS to an unnamed recipient, 1807 Sep 6 (Box 1)
      Inverness
      1 p.; 25 x 19 cm.
      Wishes to pack and send his wine
      coolers to Dublin.
      d.195/41
  - ELY, JOHN LOFTUS, 2ND MARQUIS OF, 1770-1845
    - AL to [Henry] Colburn (d. 1855) (Box 1)
      Tunbridge Wells
      Orders the memoirs of John Churchill,
      1st duke of Marlborough (1650-1722),
      compiled by William Coxe (1748-1828).
      d.195/42
  - ELY, JOHN LOFTUS, 2ND MARQUIS OF, 1770-1845
    - 3 AL (in third person) in French to Bosange and Co., booksellers, 1820-22 (Box 1)
      1820 Jan 5 and Jan 28
      1822 Nov 10
      Bifrons
      4 p.; 23 x 19 cm.
      Concern books.
      d.195/43-45
  - EXETER, BROWNLOW CECIL, 9TH EARL OF, 1725-1793
    - ALS to [Samuel] Ireland (d. 1800), 1785 Jun 1 (Box 1)
      1 p.; 22 x 19 cm.
      Concerns finances.
      d.195/47
  - EXETER, BROWNLOW CECIL, 9TH EARL OF, 1725-1793
    - AL to Mr. Nicols [?John Nichols (1745-1826)], 1790 Oct 3 (Box 1)
      Burghley
      1 p.; 20 x 19 cm.
      Refers Mr. Nicols to Lord Harborough.
      d.195/48
  - EXETER, BROWNLOW CECIL, 3RD MARQUIS OF, 1795-1867
    - ALS to an unnamed recipient, n.d. (Box 1)
      Asks that an enclosure (missing) be
      sent by the foreign post.
      d.195/51
  - EXETER, HENRY CECIL, 1ST MARQUIS OF, 1754-1804
    - ALS to Mr. Molteno of the Molteno firm in Pall Mall, 1803 Jun 7 (Box 1)
      [Burghley]
      1 p.; 20 x 16 cm.
      Returns two pictures, a view of Paris
      by Thomas Girtin (1775-1802) and
      another by Walker [James Walker?
      (1748-1808?)].
      d.195/50
  - HEADFORT, MARY (QUIN) TAYLOR, MARCHIONESS OF, 1758-1842
    - AL to Mr. Butler, 1799 Dec 7 (Box 1)
      26 Albemarle Street
      Sends an invitation for Mr. Butler
      to call.
      d.195/64
  - HEADFORT, MARY (QUIN) TAYLOR, MARCHIONESS OF, 1758-1842
    - AL to Henry Colburn (d. 1855), 1819 May 18 (Box 1)
      West End House
      Desires to exchange her copy of
      "Emmeline" with one bound in calf
      and gilt.
      d.195/61
  - HEADFORT, THOMAS TAYLOR, 1ST MARQUIS OF, 1757-1829
    - 3 ALS and 1 AL to Paget, Bainbridge and Co., bankers, 1801-1808 (Box 1)
      various places
      4 p.; 24 x 19 cm.
      Personal banking transactions.
      d.195/57-60
  - HEADFORT, THOMAS TAYLOR, 2ND MARQUIS OF, 1787-1870
    - ALS to an unnamed recipient, [bef. 1829] (Box 1)
      [before 1829] Feb 7, Gould's Hotel
      Encloses a paper (missing) concerning
      the Marquess of Headfort's health.
      d.195/63
  - HERTFORD, FRANCIS CONWAY, 5TH MARQUIS OF, 1743-1822
    - ALS to an unnamed recipient, n.d. (Box 1)
      [after 1807] n.d.
      Orford, Woodbridge
      Wishes to know if any cadets will be
      sent to India in the coming year.
      d.195/66
  - HERTFORD, FRANCIS CONWAY, 5TH MARQUIS OF, 1743-1822
    - AL to the Lord Mayor Elect and Sheriffs [of London], 1817 Nov 1 (Box 1)
      Orford
      d.195/67
  - HERTFORD, FRANCIS CONWAY, 5TH MARQUIS OF, 1743-1822
    - Letter (in the hand of Isabella Anne (Ingram Shepheard) Ingram-Seymour- Conway, Marchioness of Hertford, 1760- 1834) to the Royal Humane Society, 1821 Oct 29 (Box 1)
      Sudbourn Hall
      Accepts an honor bestowed upon him
      by the society.
      d.195/68
  - HERTFORD, FRANCIS SEYMOUR-CONWAY, MARQUIS OF, 1777-1842
    - ALS to an unnamed recipient, [bef. 1822] (Box 1)
      Seymour Terrace[?]
      Declines an offer of wine.
      d.195/69
  - HERTFORD, FRANCIS SEYMOUR-CONWAY, MARQUIS OF, 1777-1842
    - ALS in French to Mr. Benelli, n.d. (Box 1)
      Declines to receive any more
      paintings as he has no more space
      describes his voyage home from Paris.
      d.195/70
  - HERTFORD, ISABELLA ANNE, MARCHIONESS OF, 1760-1834
    - ALS to an unnamed recipient, 1816 Mar 1 (Box 1)
      Brighton
      She will subscribe to a book.
      d.195/67x
  - KERR, LORD CHARLES BEAUCHAMP, 1775-1816
    - ALS to an unnamed recipient, 1815 Aug 30 (Box 1)
      Inquires about a receipt.
      d.195/80
  - LANSDOWNE, HENRY PETTY-FITZMAURICE, MARQUIS OF, 1780-1863
    - AL to J. Bainbridge of Paget, Bainbridge and Co., bankers, [1814] Apr 20 (Box 1)
      Lansdowne House
      Sends his annual subscription to the
      St. Patrick's Society.
      d.195/72
  - LANSDOWNE, HENRY PETTY-FITZMAURICE, MARQUIS OF, 1780-1863
    - AL to the Athenaeum, 1824 Jul 19 (Box 1)
      Bowood
      2 p.; 23 x 19 cm.
      Cannot attend the weekly meeting
      proposes William Brougham, 2nd baron
      Brougham and Vaux (1795-1886) for
      membership.
      d.195/75
  - LANSDOWNE, LOUISA EMMA, MARCHIONESS OF, 1785-1851
    - AL to [Sir Richard] Westmacott (1775-1856), 1819 n.d. (Box 1)
      1 p.; 19 x 12 cm.
      Thanks Westmacott for a ticket to an
      exhibition.
      d.195/75x
  - LANSDOWNE, LOUISA EMMA, MARCHIONESS OF, 1785-1851
    - ALS to Robert Lovell Gwatkin (1757-1843), 1804 Aug 23 (Box 1)
      Melbury
      Informs him that Mrs. Campbell has
      safely arrived and discusses the
      whooping cough of "little Mary."
      d.195/75xx
  - LONDONDERRY, LORD
    - ALS to Canning [?Stratford Canning, 1st viscount Stratford de Redcliffe (1786-1880)], n.d. (Box 1)
      3 p.; 18 x 12 cm.
      His sister, Elizabeth, tells him his
      portrait needs yet another sitting.
      d.195/76xx
  - LOTHIAN, JOHN WILLIAM ROBERT KERR, MARQUIS OF, 1794-1841
    - AL to the Lord Mayor Elect [of London], 1819 Nov 8 (Box 1)
      St. James Square
      Accepts an invitation to dine.
      d.195/79
  - LOTHIAN, WILLIAM KERR, 6TH MARQUIS OF, 1763-1824
    - ALS to Lackington and Co., booksellers, [1819] (Box 1)
      [1819 or later] Sep 16
      Montagu House, Whitehall
      Accepts and thanks for the portraits
      d.195/77
  - LOTHIAN, WILLIAM KERR, 6TH MARQUIS OF, 1763-1824
    - ALS to Lackington and Co., booksellers, 1820 Sep 28 (Box 1)
      2 p.; 24 x 19 cm.
      Has spoken to Henry James
      Montagu-Scott, baron Montagu
      (1776-1845) on the matter of the
      late Charles William Henry Montagu
      Scott, 4th duke of Buccleugh
      (1772-1819) and thanks for the proof
      prints which he returns.
      d.195/78
  - LOTHIAN, WILLIAM KERR, 6TH MARQUIS OF, 1763-1824
    - ALS to an unnamed recipient, [no yr] Jun 14 (Box 1)
      Northallerton
      1 p.; 21 x 19 cm.
      Places an order.
      d.195/76xxxx
  - MOORE, LORD H.
    - AL to Paget, Bainbridge and Co., bankers, 1806 Jun 15 (Box 1)
      Manchester House
      Concerns personal finances.
      d.195/36xx
  - NORTHAMPTON, CHARLES COMPTON, 1ST MARQUIS OF, 1760-1828
    - AL to Lackington and Co., booksellers, 1818 May 28 (Box 1)
      Castle Abbey
      Desires that the portraits by sent
      to Lady Frances Compton.
      d.195/81x
  - O'BRYEN, LORD EDWARD, D. 1824
    - ALS to an unnamed recipient, 1815 Nov 10 (Box 1)
      Chippenham
      Sends a change of address.
      d.195/102
  - ORMONDE, ANNE MARIA CATHERINE, MARCHIONESS OF, 1789-1817
    - ALS to an unnamed recipient, 1801 Dec 3 (Box 1)
      Castlecomer
      Asks to discontinue her advertisement
      for a colliery manager.
      d.195/85
  - ORMONDE, ANNE MARIA CATHERINE, MARCHIONESS OF, 1789-1817
    - ALS to an unnamed recipient, 1804 Jan 9 (Box 1)
      Requests information about accounts.
      d.195/86
  - ORMONDE, JAMES BUTLER, 5TH MARQUIS OF, 1774-1838
    - AL to Thomas Wallace, baron, 1768-1844, [no yr] May 26 (Box 1)
      d.195/87
  - ORMONDE, WALTER BUTLER, MARQUIS OF, 1770-1820
    - AL to Gavrell and Jones, firm, [1820] (Box 1)
      Radbourne, Derby
      Request for newpapers.
      d.195/82
  - ORMONDE, WALTER BUTLER, MARQUIS OF, 1770-1820
    - 2 ALS to Paget, Bainbridge and Co., bankers, 1801 Jan (Box 1)
      Kilkenny
      Drafts drawn.
      d.195/82x, 83
  - ORMONDE, WALTER BUTLER, MARQUIS OF, 1770-1820
    - AL to Mr. Paget of Paget, Bainbridge and Co., bankers (Box 1)
      Concerns the date of a past draft.
      d.195/84
  - QUEENSBERRY, CHARLES DOUGLAS, 6TH MARQUIS OF, 1777-1837
    - AL to the Lord Mayor Elect and Sheriffs [of London], 1827 Oct 17 (Box 1)
      Declines an invitation.
      d.195/91x
  - SALISBURY, JAMES CECIL, 1ST MARQUIS OF, 1748-1823
    - ALS to an unnamed recipient, 1791 Sep 7 (Box 1)
      Hatfield
      1 p.; 20 x 17 cm.
      Concerns items engraved and to be
      engraved in conjunction with "the
      Archery Meeting" and the "Silver
      Arrow" prize which he and Joseph
      Cotton (1745-1825) had won.
      d.195/91xx
  - SALISBURY, JAMES CECIL, 1ST MARQUIS OF, 1748-1823
    - AL to the Lord Mayor Elect and the Sheriffs [of London], 1790 Nov 1 (Box 1)
      Dover Castle
      d.195/92x
  - SALISBURY, JAMES CECIL, 1ST MARQUIS OF, 1748-1823
    - AL to the Lord Mayor and Sheriffs [of London], 1801 Nov 4 (Box 1)
      d.195/93
  - SALISBURY, JAMES CECIL, 1ST MARQUIS OF, 1748-1823
    - AL (in third person) to an unnamed recipient, 1816 Apr 25 (Box 1)
      1 p.; 10 x 16 cm.
      Order of six "printed card tickets."
      d.195/93x
  - SALISBURY, JAMES GASCOYNE-CECIL, 2ND MARQUIS OF, 1791-1868
    - AL to the Lord Mayor Elect and the Sheriffs [of London], 1813 Nov (Box 1)
      1 p.; 8 x 12 cm.
      d.195/92xx
  - SALISBURY, JAMES, 2ND MARQUIS OF, 1791-1868
    - AL to Mr. Parker, [before 1823] (Box 1)
      Requests his gun and will send more
      for repair.
      d.195/95
  - SALISBURY, JAMES GASCOYNE-CECIL, 2ND MARQUIS OF, 1791-1868
    - AL (in French) to Mr. Bossange, 1847 Jul 30 (Box 1)
      Orders a French-Spanish grammar
      presumably for travel purposes.
      d.195/95x
  - THOMOND, MARY (PALMER) O'BRIEN, MARCHIONESS OF, 1750-1820
    - ALS to an unnamed recipient, [1808 or later] (Box 1)
      d.195/101
  - THOMOND, MURROUGH O'BRIEN, MARQUIS OF, 1726-1808
    - AL to George Shepheard (1770-1842), 1794 Sep 19 (Box 1)
      Taplow
      Will see him next week.
      d.195/97
  - THOMOND, WILLIAM O'BRIEN, 2ND MARQUIS OF, 1768-1846
    - Signature, 1820 Sep 5 (Box 1)
      1 p.; 12 x 18 cm.
      On a note of admission to the House
      of Lords.
      d.195/100
  - THOMOND, WILLIAM O'BRIEN, 2ND MARQUIS OF, 1768-1846
    - 2 ALS to unnamed recipients, 1817-18 (Box 1)
      1817 [Dec?] 20 and 1818 Jan 1
      Cheltenham
      3 p.; 18 x 11 cm.
      Draft for £100 missing and then
      recovered.
      d.195/98,99
  - THYNNE, LORD JOHN, 1798-1881
    - 2 AL to Benjamin Lewis Vulliamy (1780-1854), n.d. (Box 1)
      [1820 or later (paper watermark
      1820)] and n.d.
      St. James's Square
      Request to move a clock and
      directions on its placement in the
      new location.
      d.195/16,17
  - TWEEDDALE, GEORGE HAY, 8TH MARQUIS OF, 1787-1876
    - [Memorandum]: autograph MS, 1820 Sep 5 (Box 1)
      1 p.; 18 x 22 cm.
      A pass to the House of Lords.
      d.195/104xx
  - WATERFORD, SUSANNA BERESFORD, MARCHIONESS OF, 1784-1827
    - AL to Lackington and Co., booksellers, 1807 Oct 30 (Box 1)
      George Street
      Requests the bill for and discusses
      the additions to her library.
      d.195/105